This heist is about to go into overdrive.
Drive Hard is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Brian Trenchard-Smith.
A former race car driver is abducted by a mysterious thief and forced to be the wheel-man
for a crime that puts them both in the sights of the cops and the mob.
Simon Keller, played by John Cusack.
Peter Roberts, played by Thomas Jane.
Agent Walker, played by Zoe Ventoura.
Rossi, played by Christopher Morris.
Tessa Roberts, played by Yesse Spence.
Detective Chief Inspector Smith, played by Damien Garvey.
Drive Hard (originally titled Hard Drive) is a 2014 Australian buddy action film directed by
Brian Trenchard-Smith and written by Chad Law, Evan Law, and Trenchard-Smith.
A professional thief (John Cusack) takes a former race car driver (Thomas
Jane) hostage and forces him to drive his getaway car.
The film explores themes of getaway driver, heist
gone wrong, professional thief.
The tone is lighthearted.